The reason I'm such a fan of Rockefeller
is because of one very important lesson
that I learned from the letters that he sent his son,
which was he tells a story of how
he was the second largest oil producer,
and he went to go try and buy the largest producer.
And the guy rebuffed him a bunch of times
every time he tried to buy,
and then finally he was able to get a deal done,
and he way overpaid for this facility.
And the guy was laughing at him saying,
well, you know, you're an idiot,
I can't believe you paid this much for my business.
And then the next 30 days he did something like 24 deals.
And the reason he was able to do those 24 deals
is because once he was number two and bought the number one,
he had such a significant part of the market share
that he was able to say he was number one in the market.
And with that story, he was able to do 24 more deals
that were significantly more lucrative.
And so what I learned from that was the value of the story.
So there was the price of the assets in the business,
and then everything that he paid in excess,
he paid to do one thing,
which was to be able to say that he was number one,
so that he had the leverage in the rest of the negotiations.
And so it was really shifting from this, like,
I have to get an amazing deal in every single thing I do,
which happens across business all the time,
to taking a step back at the global outlook
of like battles and wars,
like I'm willing to lose battles to win wars.